

704-241-2153 | bjschwa2@gmail.com | www.bradleyschwarz.com | bjschwa2

### Summary\_

Current UI/UX Engineer at Aqueti. 4+ years experience specializing in frontend development, interface design, and making complex systems easy to use. I enjoy looking at the fundamental aspects of something and examining its meaning and the purpose it brings to the world, oh and making it pretty too.

## Work Experience

Aqueti Inc. Durham, NC

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Sept. 2016 - Present

- · Lead a small team to create a distributed ecosystem for viewing, and maintaining Aqueti camera systems
- · Designed and build Vue Electron Application Client for camera specific viewing Experience
- · Designed, built, and deployed Vue progressive web application for administrative management of Aqueti camera systems
- · Designed an overall service architecture and pipelines for supplying high quality streaming to browsers using GStreamer and WebRTC
- Implemented Socket.io API layer for Aqueti OS allowing for cross platform applications integration
- · Assisted in designing C API for Aqueti OS
- · Designed and Implemented various QT applications for setup, maintenance, and operation of Aqueti camera systems
- · Participated in the design and implementation of a scalable image acquisition and and compositing system consisting of high resolution multisensor camera arrays with distributed rendering and storage

**Oscar Labs** Raleigh, NC

- SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Jan. 2014 - May. 2016 Participated in the design of a web application to track and organize projects
- · Assisted with the development and maintenance of various Django applications

### Education

#### **North Carolina State University**

Raleigh, NC

**B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING** 

Aug. 2012 - May. 2016

• Minor in Cognitive Science

# **Extracurricular Activity**

#### **NC State Human Factors and Ergonomics**

Raleigh, NC

COGNITIVE PSYCHOLOGY RESEARCH

Jan. 2018 - Present

- · Designed and implemented study to determine correlations between mindfulness and aspects of cognition
- Designed study to examine the potential negative effects of mindfulness and automated tasks

### Skills\_

**Back-end** Django, REST API, Socket.io, Flask, QT **Front-end** HTML5, Vue, Electron, Vuetify, Bootstrap **Programming** Node.js, Python, LaTeX, JavaScript, C, C++, CSS

## Additional Experience \_\_\_\_

2012 Eagle Scout, Boy Scouts of America Charlotte, NC Raleigh, NC

2011 Fine Arts, The Governors School of North Carolina

OCTOBER 27, 2018 BRADLEY SCHWARZ · RÉSUMÉ